[{"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "You guys want to step in?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "I'm Betty.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Identify yourselves?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "Three generations of family?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "It made you appreciate hot water, flushing toilets, electricity.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "So what was it like?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: We did.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "But you came through it as a family?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes, the first night was rough because we were tilting very badly.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Were you worried at any point it might not end this way?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Yes, very badly.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "The ship was listing, right?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "For me, it was really scary because it's never happened to me, and it's my first cruise.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "And what was it like for you guys?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Good to have your mom and grand mom and everybody with you, so you were safe?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I actually have one booked in June for Alaska.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "So, are you going to go on a cruise again?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I had packed some cards.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "How do you past the time?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "I feel like they didn't start off right.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Are you, and are you going to sue them?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "It was constantly changing.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Did you think they kept you informed, and do you feel you were constantly given the right information?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, I think the most important thing is definitely get to a warm shower, a nice bed, and get some rest, because honestly, time will tell what we're going to see in the next couple days from this.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Are they safe and sound if they're feeling OK or not?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "This is Rusty, right?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Excited to be on land.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Do you think you realized because of this and because of what happened, maybe if it was a regular cruise you might not feel this way, and now you appreciate them in a way you didn't?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Oh, my word.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Your mom and dad, what was it like to see her?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "To the hotel to eat, I hope.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Where are you headed now?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Yes, it was.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "This was your surprise 40th birthday party?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "They fed us lots of food.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What did you have for food?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, and they got the toilets working today, so we have been using those but probably a hot shower is probably what our pro priority is.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Which would you prefer, a shower or a toilet?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "It was kind of crazy, for sure.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "So how was it?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "They're back in Kansas City, in Topeka.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "AVIDGE: And where are they right now?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "He's a platinum member.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "I mean, how is it we see you and other still people waiting?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "It's -- well, today, the mood kind of turned negative, as everyone started listening to what was happening onshore.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "And what has it been like just in the past few hours here waiting to finally finish this ordeal?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Yes, tweets are just cathartic to me.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "You know, just tell us about -- was that a cathartic type of thing?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I have a sweater on right now, but I brought about five books and eight magazines and we have read them al cover to cover.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "You actually have a coat and are not freezing?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Did that happen for you also?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Well, the worst was -- I'm going to have to say the fire.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What was the -- if there's a moment, you talk about what was the worst single thing that happened and maybe the best single thing that happened to you?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Well, get on that.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Glad to be on land, for sure.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "New Orleans, and then fly out tomorrow to South Carolina.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "To get on the bus to go to New Orleans?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "LOVE: When we could see land.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "That we're almost home?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "No, but it was 2 1/2 days of great fun, and then the rest of the time, it was family coming together, bonding.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And not to say you're the trouble maker, but this did not go in any way that this family thought, did it?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "At times, yes.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Did you really feel the rough seas?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Grounded.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "And how do you feel?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "No, when we were standing at the doors, I said, it still doesn't seem like it's happening.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Has it finally sunk in?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Pray.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "What do you do?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, we did.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Did you meet new people through that?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "It was creepy.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "What happens after the sun goes down?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "So will you ever go again?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "I probably won't, but I don't know.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "How do you get that out of your mind?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "We're friends.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "Are you friends or dating?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "A lot of cards were played.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "How did you spend the time?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "The first day, we slept at 6:00.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "Was it there?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "Not everybody.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "You think everyone got along well?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "We tried to sleep a lot.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "Was there an organization to the day?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "130214pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "Are you going to save the robe?", "qSentId": 814}]